♪ ♪
That jeep right there,
that's your rental.
You have a good stay.
Spencer Hamilton?
That's right.
Ed Tucker.
Everything's set.
Power's on, water's
on, phone works.
You need a key?
Got one.
What's that?
My bill.
Your brother always
paid me in cash.
Oh.
Yeah, he'd usually
pay me when I got done.
That way neither
one of us forgot.
That's a good idea.
I was wondering when
somebody would come down
to close the house.
You gonna sell it?
I don't know.
I wouldn't park my car there.
We cut a limb off that tree.
It drips sap on everything.
Do you know where
my brother was killed?
Yeah.
Will you show me?
Out there?
What is that?
A duck blind?
Yeah.
Season's been over six months.
How'd it happen?
Well, the way I heard
it, Frank was in the boat.
His four buddies was
already in that blind.
A bunch of ducks come
in flying low, you know,
and Frank grabbed
his gun, stood up
just as his friend fired.
Hit Frank square in the chest.
Frank was in the boat?
That's right.
Heard he was setting decoys.
You can ask the sheriff.
It's what all the fellas said...
You know, the ones
that was there. Yeah.
Anyway, like I said,
your brother always
paid me cash.
That way neither
one of us forgot.
I ain't never seen
nothing like it.
Them big blues got
them schools of trout
and run 'em up on the beach
and I picked up two or
three bucketfuls myself.
When was that?
Yesterday.
I always miss it.
It never fails.
I get there the day
before it or the day after.
It just kills my soul.
Wouldn't you think a
person just one time
could get there the day of it?
Happens to me, too.
Boys, and that's what
brought the people down here.
The fish, water, beaches,
sun, lost colony play.
In the '50s, that was just fine,
but now we just
got too many of 'em.
Tell, 'em, Commissioner.
Wintertime...
Good for the economy.
Let's people know
where this place is at.
Good all around.
You campaigning
again, Commissioner?
I might.
I voted for you last time.
Me, too.
I voted for you when
you ran democrat,
when you ran republican
and when you ran independent.
You did?
No, but Mama did.
Said she felt sorry for you.
Well, honey, you just tell
Mama to keep on voting.
Keep on feeling
sorry for old Gordon,
but keep on voting.
Hell, Commissioner,
if you ever win,
we'll have to get out
the high school band
and have a parade.
I'm Spencer Hamilton,
Frank Hamilton's brother.
Oh... Oh, uh, have a seat.
I'm Gordon Lewis.
Commissioner?
It's a little joke.
Have something.
Did you know my brother?
Well, yeah, I knew him.
You know, it's interesting
that you should come up to me.
I've got this little law office.
Don't practice much anymore.
I got a little
insurance business,
sell some real estate
from time to time.
But I did do a couple
things for your brother.
Um, so yeah, I
knew... Who killed him?
Well, you know,
that was an accident.
Happened last November.
I've been stationed in Europe.
I just mustered out.
So, uh, you want to
step over to my little office
and go through Frank's papers...
What I got of 'em?
All I want is the name of
the man who killed him.
Well, uh...
Dalton.
Here's the man
you ought to talk to.
Spencer Hamilton...
Frank Hamilton's brother.
Sheriff Parks.
Oh, it's a pleasure to
meet you, Mr. Hamilton.
Sorry about your brother.
Who killed him?
Well, it was an accident.
Who pulled the trigger?
A man named Ryan Bartell.
You know where I can find him?
Well, haven't seen
him, or his friends.
I hear they're in town.
I know how you must
feel, but it was an accident.
You seem awfully upset.
I hope you don't feel...
You don't know how I feel.
Thanks.
You here for the fishing?
Yeah, I've heard the blue fish
run the trout right
up into your bunk.
That's right.
Been here long?
Born here.
Where you from?
Where it snows.
Ooh.
Ryan Bartell, uh, you know him?
Oh, yeah. Comes in here
all the time with his buddies.
Known Ryan long?
No. Friend of a friend.
Yeah, well, he is a card.
Loves to party, but he's
got a hell of a temper.
That right?
Oh, yeah. One night last year,
Ryan comes in
here with his pals.
And all of a sudden,
Ryan gets into a brawl
with one of his friends...
A guy by the name
of Frank Hamilton,
over some girl.
Ryan wants her, she wants Frank.
Just an argument over a girl?
Oh, yeah, well, it happens.
But it got settled.
Another girl comes in.
Now speak of the
devil. There they are.
Some beer all around.
Coming right up.
I'm Spencer Hamilton...
Frank Hamilton's brother.
I'm Ernie D'Amato.
This is David
Channing, Ryan Bartell,
and Lee Kramer.
You want something else?
No.
We're really, really sorry
about what happened to Frank.
Yeah, he, uh...
Frank-Frank was a great guy.
He was a great guy.
What about you?
How sorry are you?
I'm sorry.
It was an accident.
What happened, happened.
And that's it?
It was an accident.
Ask anybody.
I'm asking you.
Why'd you kill my brother?
I told you, it was an accident.
Frank was in the boat
when you shot him, right?
Right?
He gave his
statement to the sheriff.
Frank was in the boat?
Yeah, he was in the boat.
You're a liar.
Ryan, the man lost his brother.
You calling me a liar?
Yeah, you're a liar.
Frank wasn't in any boat.
He almost drowned
when he was three.
He had hydrophobia.
He wouldn't go near the water.
You murdered my brother.
Liar!
Hey! Hey, cut it out!
Back off!
Now tell me why you
murdered my brother!
Hey, drop the knife.
Drop the knife.
All right, what's going on here?
Ask him.
I didn't start it.
You better hold it together.
That was real dumb.
Hey, damn it, I didn't start it.
We got a problem.
Oh, yeah.
Take a die and don't look
at it until you get home.
If it's white, you go to bed.
If it's red,
you've got work to do.
And it has to be done by
7:00 a.m. Are we agreed?
Nobody talks to anybody,
including each other
until after 9:00 a.m.
Only the man that does the job
will know that he did it.
Yeah?
What for?
Yeah, yeah, okay.
I'll be there!
Hey, what the hell
took you so long?
Morning.
Show him the warrant, Clarence.
Floyd Tubbs... he
owns the barbershop...
Was out walking in
the woods this morning
about a mile from here, 6:00.
Heard pistol shots,
and went to look.
Ryan Bartell was lying there
with two bullets through him,
stone dead.
Wait a minute. I
don't even own a gun.
And I wasn't out running around
in the woods at 6:00.
I was right here.
Yeah? Yeah. Handing a mechanic
the keys to that car over there.
He came to fix the ignition.
At 6:00 in the morning?
He said he was real busy.
His work was backed up
and that was the only
time he could fix it.
What's his name? Jack.
Jack something.
Go call Jack Rose.
Yes, sir.
Sheriff.
Why are you looking at me?
Found this in the gun case.
Recently fired.
Wait a minute.
I've never seen that before.
Jack Rose said he
hadn't been anywhere near
this place this morning!
What?!
Let's go, Mr. Hamilton.
This is crazy. I
didn't kill anybody.
I hereby grant
the defense's motion,
and in so doing,
find the prosecution's
case against Horton Garrett
to be solely lacking
in substance and merit.
I therefore order that the
charges against Mr. Garrett
be dropped and that he
be released immediately.
Court is adjourned.
Thank you, Mr. Matlock.
Thank you a million times!
Ah, just doing my job.
Now you and your
wife go celebrate.
We will. Oh, we will!
Yeah.
Where's Mr. Garrett?
Free man.
Free is right.
We just got this from the bank.
His check bounced?!
Hey, Mr. Garrett!
Excuse me. Excuse me.
Just let me by.
Hey, Mr. Garrett!
Hey, fella!
I hate that.
I hate that!
Don't you just hate that?
We should only
take cash in advance.
Yeah.
Ben Matlock.
Yes, sir, General.
Uh, well, it's good to hear
your voice, General Colvin.
It's been such a long time.
Uh-huh.
Uh-huh. Uh, uh-huh.
Oh, well, sure.
Sure, I remember.
And, and...
Why, yes, sir, yes, sir, I'd
be, I'd be glad to do that.
Of course.
Yes, sir. Bye, General Colvin.
Hey, Michelle,
you know who that was?
General Colvin,
four-star general.
Big man. He did me a favor
several years ago,
and now it's my turn.
Have you ever heard of town
called Manteo on Roanoke Island
in North Carolina?
Mr. Matlock.
Yeah?
You're supposed to go straight
to the courthouse,
sir. They sent a cab.
I've been in elevators
bigger than that.
That thing bounced
like jackrabbit
all the way from Raleigh.
Well, at least you're
in good hands.
Chris there is the most
experienced pilot we've got.
Thanks, Roy.
Are you him?
Him who?
That lawyer. What lawyer?
The one they sent
for from Atlanta.
Well, I'm a lawyer.
We heard about your suit.
What suit?
Is that it?
Well, it's my suit.
Excuse me.
That's him.
That's him!
What do you think?
He's supposed to be here.
Mr. Matlock?
Yeah.
Glad to see ya.
I'm Gordon Lewis,
your co-counsel.
Well, not really co-counsel.
I was kinda holding down
the fort till you got here.
This is Spencer Hamilton.
Thanks for coming.
Oh, uh-huh, uh-huh. Well, uh...
Ooh, we better get inside.
Uh, Your Honor, Your
Honor, I'm-I'm sorry I'm late.
Mr. Matlock, this is a pleasure!
I'm Melissa Lyle,
and I have followed your career
with great admiration!
Oh, thank you.
Uh, Your Honor, at this time...
Why are you late?
I just got here.
There's a big crowd
outside. I got stuck.
I will not have that
crowd disrupting this trial,
you understand?
Well, yes, sir, but...
Good.
Now, in your absence,
your co-counsel, the prosecutor
and I have discussed bail.
And it has been agreed
that $50,000 is reasonable.
You have no objections,
do you, Mr. Matlock?
I was just holding
down the fort.
I'm not really co-counsel.
Uh, no objection.
Good. Mrs. Lyle,
anything further?
Oh, no, Your Honor.
Fine. Mr. Matlock,
if you'll sign on for the
case, we're in business.
Court's adjourned.
Okay.
Well...
Uh...
Excuse me.
You got a problem?
You paid Jack Rose to lie.
You're nuts, mister.
What the hell are
you talking about?
Which one of you killed Ryan?
Or was it all of ya?
Spencer! Get away from the car.
Get away from the car.
Spencer!
Murderers!
You know a lot a
of people down here
think you're guilty.
That, that thing you
pulled on the street,
that was dumb. I'm
talking real dumb.
I never heard of
Roanoke Island before.
And the only reason
I'm down here now is
General Colvin called
me and I owe him a favor.
He said you were
one of his best men
and you had a hot temper.
Now I'm gonna warn you.
During the course of this trial,
you be one of the best men.
Forget the hot temper part.
You got that?
Yeah.
Okay.
So, uh,
this is where he was killed?
What's his name?
Ryan Bartell.
Killed Frank over some girl.
Yeah? Yeah.
Were you and Frank close?
We're actually pretty different,
except for our temper.
What'd he do for a living?
He wheeled and
dealed in a lot of stuff.
Did pretty well, I guess.
We just started
patching things up.
How do you suppose
that gun got in your house?
I don't know.
But you were home?
Yeah, the whole time.
This mechanic, Jack
Rose, was there from...
6:00 to 7:30 fixing the car.
He told the sheriff
he was home in bed.
Hm.
Wonder why he lied.
There you go, Jack
Rose's statement.
Oh, long as we're at it, why
don't I give you a copy of this, too.
It's Conrad
McMasters' statement.
Okay. Who's Conrad McMasters?
Me.
Conrad broke up a fight
between Ryan Bartell
and your client the
day before the murder.
How?
Had my pistol.
That's all there was to
it? Yeah, pretty much.
Spencer Hamilton stuck
the knife in the table and left.
There was a knife?
Yeah. Belonged to Ryan Bartell.
Spencer had taken
it away from him,
and they got to
rassling about it, and...
Anyway, Ryan said he
didn't... he didn't start it.
Actually, they were both
pretty mad at each other, but...
But you had your pistol. Yeah.
Yeah, when I'm in
uniform, I have my pistol.
That was good work.
Thanks.
Um...
Ryan Bartell lives, uh,
on the, uh, Mother
Vineyard Road.
Sheriff?
Well, why don't
you give Mr. Matlock
a ride out there.
All right!
My first name's Ben.
Conrad.
B and C, Ben and Conrad.
Conrad and Ben.
And there's the library.
That's Gordon Kellogg's Supply.
Oh, that's a...
nice looking store.
Sell lumber...
What else they sell?
Whatever you need.
Oh, nice.
And there's your basic house.
Uh-huh. And...
as you can see, woods.
Yeah.
You like it here, huh?
Yeah. Yeah.
It's pretty much all I know.
I've traveled.
You know, I've been
to New York, Miami...
Atlanta?
Been to Atlanta.
But I always wind up back here.
Well,
you like here.
You like your job.
Yeah.
I think I'm ahead of the game.
Okay, here we are.
Boy, that's nice!
Big.
Sure doesn't look
like a time-share.
Oh, time-share?
No, Mr. Bartell
owned this place.
Paid cash for it.
Cash? Yeah.
He stay here by himself?
Sometimes.
A lot of times.
Then a lot of times he'd
bring the family along.
And... then, a lot of times he'd
come down here with another woman.
Yeah? Yeah.
Oh, yeah.
He had several.
Blondes, brunettes, redheads.
I mean, me, I just
got one, you know?
Yeah, me, too.
Do all his friends have
homes as nice as this?
Oh, yeah.
Huh.
You have any idea
what they do for a living?
Well, I'm pretty sure
they're not deputy sheriffs.
Yeah.
Huh.
How long these fellas
been coming down here?
Oh, about five years, I guess.
Huh.
Mm.
Oh, yeah.
Duck hunters, huh?
Yes, sir.
Uh-huh.
They any good?
They brag about it, give
game to the locals sometimes,
but I don't know if
they're any good.
Do you know anybody who would?
Are you kidding?
To hear them talk,
they've bagged every
duck they ever shot at.
Huh. Did you ever
go hunting with them?
Nah. They keep pretty
much to themselves.
But the town folks love
'em, don't they, Conrad?
Yeah, they get
along with everybody.
Give to charities in
town, different causes.
Huh.
Do they come in here a lot?
A lot. Have a couple beers,
and then either eat dinner
here or go to one of their houses
to play poker and
have pizzas delivered.
They play... poker a lot?
Well, uh...
they like to gamble
a little, I guess.
Sometimes the hunters run into
what you call "bluebird weather."
Clear days without any wind.
Ducks don't fly at all, so
might as well play poker.
Yeah, in-in the daytime,
but at-at night, I...
Well, I guess if you
hunt long enough,
you get to knowing when
bluebird weather's coming.
Huh. What?
This is a peculiar
bunch of duck hunters.
Play poker all night, eat pizza.
What happens to
the duck they shoot?
Don't they eat 'em?
Maybe they don't like duck.
Like to shoot 'em;
don't like to eat 'em.
Give 'em away...
Lot of people do that.
Something is wrong.
Central dispatch to
McMasters. Can you copy?
Go ahead, Clarence.
Conrad.
Conrad?
What?!
You better get over
to Jack Rose's garage.
Spencer Hamilton's there,
and he's trying to beat
the living hell out of Jack.
Great.
Do you suppose I could
just rent a car down here?
Oh, yeah!
Leave me alone... I
don't have to talk to you.
Will you stand still?
Come here! Just-just
tell me why you lied.
Get out of here!
Come here!
You're a damn liar, Rose!
Come back here!
You better get out of here!
The cops are coming!
Get out of here!
Leave me alone!
Tell me why you lied!
Open the door, Rose.
Come on out of there, Rose!
Come on out of there!
Tell me why you lied?
Come on out of there, Rose.
In another minute, I'll be
through this door, Rose.
You are some kind of maniac!
It's just gonna be
you and me, Rose.
Get out of here!
Almost there, Rose!
Hey, Spence! Hold it!
Okay!
Okay, okay.
Jack, come on out of there.
Jack! Come on
out of there.
He's not gonna hurt you.
See that?
He tried to kill me! I'm trying
to make you tell
me why you lied.
I'm gonna press charges, pal.
They're gonna electrocute
you for killing Ryan Bartell,
and they're gonna
electrocute you again
for trying to kill me!
Uh, Mr. Rose,
you can file charges,
but if you do, then
everybody's gonna wonder
what you did to make
Spencer so mad at you.
You just keep him away from me.
You think he can do that?
Count on it.
All right, then it's over.
Come on, Jack.
Come on.
Now, I told you,
and I'm gonna tell
you one more time,
don't ever try
something like this again.
But he... You're on trial
for murder!
You can't go around here
acting like some kind of a jackass.
Hell... You got that?
Yeah, I got that.
Good. 'Cause otherwise,
you're digging your own grave.
And with the
evidence against you,
it won't take much of a shovel.
Hi.
You scared the hell out of me!
Oh, I'm sorry. The
door was open.
Uh, Mr. D'Amato?
Yeah?
I'm, uh, I'm Ben Matlock,
Spencer Hamilton's lawyer.
He's a bum.
He shot Ryan
Bartell in cold blood.
Is that right? Yeah.
Hm. What's that?
It's mousse.
Chocolate mousse. Mm.
What's that?
Spaghetti sauce.
Green spaghetti sauce?
It's pesto.
This...
nice glass of wine,
a little mousse,
you forget about Heaven.
Oh, that's right.
You own a restaurant
in Boston, don't you?
Yeah. Oh.
This is nice here.
Uh...
you and your friends
bring your, uh...
uh, families down here, do you?
Yeah. They enjoy it.
Uh,
sometimes you don't?
Yeah.
Wha-What's wrong with that?
Sometimes you
bring another woman?
Who told you that? Oh,
I just heard it.
Let me tell you something,
I don't bother nobody;
nobody bothers me.
Something wrong with the gun?
Oh, no.
No, it's a nice
gun... it's just...
a little dirty.
This shot, uh, is illegal.
It's lead... you're
supposed to use
steel shot over water.
Federal law.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, I-I have to get
some next season.
Talking about...
how, uh...
Spencer Hamilton shot
Ryan Bartell in cold blood,
where were you that morning?
Are we gonna have
to go through this?
Can't get around it.
I was here.
Asleep.
Your mousse is burning.
Damn!
Enjoyed talking with you.
Yeah, it's me.
I just got a visit from
that lawyer, Matlock.
I took the wrong door.
Went in the toilet.
He's going to be a problem.
Excuse me.
Is there something
I can do for you?
Oh, hi. Uh, I'm Ben Matlock,
Spencer Hamilton's lawyer.
That's a nice boat.
I like it. Yeah.
So, you're a stock
broker from-from Chicago?
Yes.
Do you folks up there
know something we don't?
Well, we just know it first.
What I meant was,
uh, that flat-bottom boat
that's on the
trailer right there?
How do you haul that
when you don't have a
trailer hitch on your car?
Oh, there's one
on the other car.
I heard you always
drive that sports car
when you're down here.
He sold his other car to me.
I buy all my cars
from my friends.
That way, I know
what I'm getting.
What a good idea!
Ben Matlock, Spencer
Hamilton's lawyer.
You must be Lee Kramer.
That's right.
Ah.
Get your gun, David.
Let's go shoot some targets.
How about me?
I mean, you got your headset.
You can listen to some Mozart,
or the Grateful
Dead, or something.
But, uh, I'm not doing anything.
So, what do you say?
Okay. Yeah.
So, are you and David
both stock brokers?
Hell, no. I'm in oil leasing.
Oh. Dallas? Denver? Houston?
Houston.
Oh. That's an easy
way to lose your shirt,
especially these days.
Awful lot of bad
luck going around.
Yeah.
Ooh.
You want to survive, you
got to know what you're doing.
Yeah. Could I, uh, take a look?
Sure.
Thanks.
Hey, that's nice.
Take a shot.
Oh, no.
I wouldn't be able
to hit anything.
Boy, your gun is clean.
Your hunting buddies
could take lessons from you.
Ernie D'Amato's
gun's dirty, rusty.
So's Ryan's.
City boys. What
can you do, right?
Yeah.
Uh, were you shooting the
morning Ryan was killed?
At 6:00?
I was asleep.
At home. Alone.
Look, if I'd have
killed Ryan Bartell,
I wouldn't have needed two
shots to bring him down, you know?
Well, you got a point.
Oh!
There you go.
Hey.
Boy!
There's a lot of
people down here.
Summer time. They
come from all over.
Well, I-I don't blame them.
It's pretty down here.
Have, uh, have you
been here all your life?
Like the fella says, not yet.
What do you think?
Afraid I'm past it.
Do you remember?
Fondly.
Sheriff, those,
uh, those fellas,
those hunting fellas...
uh, how did they
get to be friends?
I mean, uh, one's from Houston.
One's from Boston.
One's from Chicago.
I mean, they're from all over.
Well, the story is,
they met on vacation,
liked one another,
and they started
meeting at different places
and taking little trips together
and wound up here.
Huh. Wound up here.
Sheriff! Mr. Matlock!
Hello, Commissioner.
Oh. Mr. Lilley.
What they say about you is true.
You are everywhere.
I like to keep up.
But you? You're the
one that's everywhere.
Oh... Isn't he, Sheriff?
Uh, he's a little young, yet.
See you later, boys.
See you, Sheriff.
I heard you was over here.
You, uh, making any
progress on your case?
Oh, you know, asking
a few questions around.
So, uh, county
commissioner, huh?
Oh, no, no.
I've run for commissioner
a lot of times.
Never won?
Never did.
Pretty soon, folks just started
calling me "Commissioner."
Oh.
Ex-officio, huh?
Yeah. Hell, I like a good joke.
Yeah.
But in the meantime,
I got my little practice,
insurance business,
one-third interest
in a used car lot.
Huh.
So, you making some
progress on that case, huh?
Well, yeah. Moderate, moderate.
Ben Matlock.
Who is this?
Elizabethan Gardens?
Well, I guess so, but...
♪ ♪
What's going on?
I got a call, anonymous.
Uh, a person fitting
your description
was seen buying or
accepting a substance
at Whalebone
Junction on the beach.
And they said this
car was here, too.
Well, you don't think
I got dope in my car?
Well, I doubt it,
and I hope not,
but I'm going to have to ask
you to open your car, Mr. Matlock.
Well...
Well, that...
This just caps this day.
Hey.
Sorry, but, uh,
trunk, too, Conrad.
Well, uh...
Uh...
What is that?
What...
Hmm.
Cocaine.
Looks like about four ounces.
What the hell's cocaine doing...
Well, surely you...
Surely you don't...
You don't think that...
How the hell could
you drag me in...
You know I had no choice!
Gentlemen!
Mr. Matlock, I will have order!
Your Honor, I was framed!
Mr. Matlock,
you're out of turn!
In my court, we
follow procedure.
Now, we're going to
go through with this.
We have to.
Now, you will speak
when you're spoken to.
You understand?
I understand.
Counsel for the defense?
I'm counsel for the defense.
I said you'll speak when...
You spoke to me!
The charge is illegal possession
of a controlled substance.
No, no, that's...
Now, we know you possessed it.
We'll find out if
you intended to sell.
No. How do you plead?
Somebody planted
that cocaine in my car!
How do you plead?!
Not guilty!
You know damn well that cocaine
doesn't belong to me.
Mr. Matlock, one
more outburst like that
and I'll charge
you with contempt!
Understood? Yes!
I understand.
Good.
The record will
reflect the entry
of a "not guilty"
plea to the charges.
We will proceed
to the matter of bail.
Does the prosecution
have any recommendations?
Oh, yes, Your Honor.
Because Mr. Matlock is
defending a case in Manio,
the people are not concerned
that he will fail
to appear for trial.
So, we recommend
that the bail be set at $10,000.
$10,000?
Tell the truth. You
don't take dope.
No, I don't take dope!
How is this going to
affect the case, sir?
Now, now, listen!
I came down here for one reason.
To defend a man that
I believe is innocent,
and if you think I'll
jeopardize my chances
by smoking cocaine
or whatever the hell else
you do with it, then you
got a... Another think...
And I'll tell you
something else.
Just because you
come from a small town,
doesn't give you the right...
And I'm telling you
something. What?
Wait. Mr. Matlock?
But you got to calm down!
But I was framed!
I believe you!
All right?
Now, somebody
planted that cocaine
because you're getting
close to something.
Yeah.
Now, we're going to
get to the bottom of this,
but you got to keep cool.
Yeah. Keep cool.
Yeah. Yeah.
Keep cool.
Mmm, boy. That was good.
Yeah, you were just hungry.
Nothing evens a man out
like a couple of eggs over easy
and a cup of hot coffee.
Eggs over easy, cup of coffee.
That's right.
Conrad, you're a good cook.
Some girl's gonna
be lucky to get you.
Well, if I say so
myself, who shouldn't.
Yeah?
Well, you keep a
nice place, I'll say that.
Thank you.
Look at all this stuff here.
What's that?
Yeah, I used to mess
around on the rodeo circuit.
A little riding,
a little roping.
First place.
That don't sound like
just messing around.
I had some fun.
I'm no Charlie Sampson.
He's good, isn't he?
You like the rodeo?
I like to watch.
You know, for a
small town fella,
you don't seem to
mind a little excitement.
Maybe you enjoy it.
If it doesn't get out of hand.
Been getting enough
of it lately though, huh?
Oh, too much, too much.
I'll tell you something, if
these fellas who framed me
think they're gonna
get away with it,
it ain't gonna happen,
it ain't gonna happen.
I'll tell ya, as soon as I
get the first little glimmer,
that's right, relax.
Exactly.
These for show?
I mess around a
little bit now and then.
Okay.
Let's see...
I got one.
♪ When it's peach
pickin' time in Georgia ♪
Ah.
♪ Apple pickin'
time in Tennessee ♪
♪ Cotton pickin'
time in Mississippi ♪
♪ Everybody picks on me ♪
♪ When it's round
up time in Texas ♪
♪ The cows all make whoopee ♪
♪ Way down south in Alabama ♪
♪ It's gal pickin' time to me ♪
♪ I hope the preacher
knows his business ♪
♪ I know he can't fool me ♪
♪ When it's peach
pickin' time in Georgia ♪
♪ It's gal pickin' time for me ♪
I cannot yodel.
You yodel.
Universal language. Universal.
I got to tell you something.
This day wound up a
lot better than it started.
Yeah.
Yeah, two eggs...
Over easy. Coffee.
Yeah, a little tune.
I can't tell you how
much I appreciate it.
Glad to see you
feeling good. I feel good.
And calm. You feel calm?
Oh, yeah.
Calm, yeah.
All right.
Which one of you framed me?
Or was it all of you?
Man's crazy.
What the hell you talking about?
I came to Manteo
to defend a client...
That's business... But
whoever framed me
just made it personal.
Got nothing to do with us, Ben.
You're a liar.
Who you calling a liar?
Calling you a liar.
You're all liars.
Now, hold it, hold it,
hold it, hold it, hold on.
You got no reason to
make such an accusation.
You lied about everything.
You lied about Frank
Hamilton's death.
He was a hydrophobic.
He wouldn't set
foot near the water,
never mind get in a boat,
and when Ryan Bartell
killed him, you all got together
to make it look like
a hunting accident.
Then, you all told
the same story,
and when Spencer
Hamilton came to town,
confronted Ryan Bartell,
next morning,
Ryan Bartell is dead.
Spencer didn't kill him.
He had an alibi.
Jack Rose... Jack Rose lied,
afraid he would wind up
like Ryan Bartell.
Now, sooner or later, one or
all of you will make a mistake,
and I'll be there
to watch you do it.
I'm going to find out why you
killed Ryan Bartell
and what you're up to.
I'll see you in court.
One more time.
Yes, sir.
Having a bad day?
Happens to the best of us.
You have got to be new in town.
Because, if I'd seen you before,
I'd remember.
Just drove in this
morning from Richmond.
Welcome to Dare County.
David Channing.
Michelle Thomas.
How long you here for?
I don't know.
Couple weeks, maybe longer.
You here by yourself?
So far.
Maybe we could have dinner.
Maybe.
Ben Matlock, hey.
Yeah. Hey, Ben.
Yeah?
I got something to tell you
that's going to
knock your hat off.
What? Well,
I got me an idea.
I just had to follow
through on it. What?
Well, you know
Jack Rose's garage?
Yeah. Yeah.
This fellow works there...
Ned... Ned, uh Porter.
Yeah. And, uh, he pumps gas,
checks oil, water,
tires, stuff like that.
Yeah. Yeah.
Well, I went there,
and I got me some gas,
and I got my oil
checked, water, tires,
stuff like that. Uh-huh.
All right, okay, okay.
Anyway, I know Ned.
Yeah. See? See?
Ned likes to talk.
Yeah?
The money for Jack
Rose's garage was put up
by Lee Kramer, David
Channing, Ernie D'Amato
and the late Frank
Hamilton and Ryan Bartell.
It's beautiful.
Mm.
Sure is.
Here's to...
new friends.
How about a walk on the beach?
Yeah.
Uh, expecting a phone call.
Business.
Oh.
What business are you in?
Real estate.
I buy property,
develop it, sell.
Ah.
Don't go away.
Uh, yeah, I've got it.
2:00, Bags Bay.
Yeah, I've got it.
Make it a twin if you can.
Okay.
See you tomorrow.
Thought you were
admiring the view.
It's getting chilly outside.
That's fine. That's fine.
Let's get the
champagne, and then...
you and I will get
better acquainted.
You know what I really need?
What's that?
About ten hours sleep.
It's a long drive from Richmond.
What is this?
I'm just asking
for a rain check.
I'm asleep on my feet.
How about...
if I take you to lunch tomorrow?
Well, I can't make lunch.
How about drinks? 4:00.
Sounds great.
Should I keep the
whole evening free?
Oh, yeah.
I can find my way out.
Tomorrow.
Yeah.
Hey.
Hi, Michelle. Sit down.
Hi. You didn't have any trouble?
No, no.
Hey, my little evening
with David paid off.
I have something. All right.
I got a look at his date book.
He travels a lot.
Europe, South
America, the Bahamas.
Oh. The finest hotels.
You wonder when he has time
to take care of his
real estate business.
So, I called the Illinois
Board of Realty. Oh?
He's not in real estate.
Yes, he is... in a big way.
He got into it overnight.
He bought a row of houses,
he tore them all down
and put up new, very
expensive houses.
Oh. They sell?
Not yet.
Takes a lot of money.
Yeah.
Sorry I'm late. MATLOCK:
Oh, sit down, Conrad.
Conrad McMasters,
Michelle Thomas, my associate.
How are you? Hi. Good.
Just talked to
the Boston Police.
You call them, they ask you
what department you want.
See, now, that's a police force.
Anyway, Ernie D'Amato...
He's got a restaurant in town.
Not doing too good.
No liquor license.
Now, the police record...
Busted six years ago.
Cocaine: possession
with intent to sell.
Well, we've all
made phone calls.
A friend in oil in Houston...
Knows everybody.
Uh, he said that Lee Kramer
is known for three things.
Of course, he, uh...
he likes women.
Puts pistachio nuts in his,
uh, chili.
Keeps drilling oil
wells that turn up dry.
But they're spending
money like they invented it.
Yeah.
Somebody put that
cocaine in my car.
They're running drugs.
The Lost Colony.
McMASTERS: Yeah.
It's a good, good place
It's been going on every summer
for 50-some years.
Mm. This is where the...
the first English colony lived?
Mm-hmm, on Roanoke Island.
And no one knows
what happened to them?
Mm-mm, no.
You know, the
old-timers say that...
on a full moon, a pure white doe
can be seen out
on the sand dunes.
They say that's the
spirit of Virginia Dare.
Uh-huh?
Gives you the chills, don't it?
Yeah. Yeah.
Ah.
What's going on?
What's this all about? Well,
uh, we're-we're making
progress with your case,
but we have something to tell
you that isn't, uh, simple or pleasant.
Let's have it.
We believe your brother and
Ryan Bartell and the others
were running drugs.
The remaining three still are.
That's what Frank
meant in his last letter.
He said he was
involved in something
that had to go
sour sooner or later.
That's, uh...
that's why he was killed.
McMASTERS: He wanted out.
David arranged a meeting
with someone for 2:00 today
at Bags Bay.
I didn't hear everything,
but I did hear him say,
"Make it a twin if you can."
Twin-engine seaplane?
Running drugs
from South America.
I think he could've
arranged something.
McMASTERS: A party? - Yeah.
Get the sheriff
and make it official?
Yeah.
All right, you boys,
spread out that way.
Jackson, head over that way.
Come on.
Down over here
on this side, go on.
All right, now, let's
see what you got.
It's almost 2:00.
Where the hell are they?
If the plane
shows, they'll show.
There's something!
That's it.
Clarence, everybody
keep down and sit tight.
Something's wrong.
He's pulling out.
Clarence, hit the beach. Now.
You in the plane,
hold it right there!
Out of the plane!
Hold it right there!
Don't move!
Come on, get out of there!
All right, easy, easy.
I don't get it. Why
didn't they show?
Conrad!
Well, at least we got the drugs.
Check if they're in the back.
We don't have
diddly! It's empty!
Nothing. What?!
Conrad... Rip
everything out of there.
Rip out the seat cushions,
pontoons... Move! Come on!
There's nothing
in there, Conrad!
There's got to be
something in there!
Do you have any
idea how much it costs
to bring these men and
equipment out here, Conrad?
I'll see you back at the office.
Man. He... he's
gonna have my head.
Hey, fella.
I want to talk to you.
What the hell happened?
Calm down, all they got
was an empty airplane.
We needed that plane.
All right.
We'll use the backup.
They're still over
at the sheriff's office
trying to figure it out.
The boat.
Fast.
How did they know
about the plane?
One of us spilled it.
You were in a dinner
last night, David.
I told you I had a date.
This blonde... who is she?
Just a blonde.
She's just a...
I think she was
looking at my date book.
You suppose she is
working with that lawyer?
You jackass.
Be on the dock across from
the Elizabeth II, 5:00 sharp.
Any sign of David?
Come on.
All right? Yeah.
Home free, boys,
we're home free.
Pull it alongside.
Just toss these right in.
Everybody, freeze!
All right, all of you,
hit the deck, come on.
Hands in plain
sight, move, come on!
Come on, let's go.
Okay, clear.
Well, I got to hand it to
you, Conrad, you were right.
Yeah, well, that seaplane pilot
this afternoon
realized, you know,
looking at the pros and cons,
that if he cooperated with me,
he might limit his time in jail.
Yeah, so...
So he told me about the backup.
I wonder if the sheriff'll
give me my head back now.
Oh, yeah, he'll give it back
and make sure it looks nice.
What's the charge?
Conspiracy to deliver a
controlled substance, maybe?
Try tax evasion.
They weren't smuggling drugs in,
they were smuggling
drug money out.
Hey, hey, hey, wait a
minute, wait a minute.
What?
When you arrested
these three birds,
they were each carrying
a million-and-a-half dollars.
That's right. And according
to the seaplane pilot,
they were illegally
moving it to offshore banks.
Yeah.
No cocaine?
That's right.
We searched the houses
and no cocaine.
That's right,
they don't deal drugs here,
they just bring
the money through.
Where did the cocaine
found in my car come from?
Uh...
Suppose there's somebody else?
Somebody else? Yeah.
They were taking their
money out of Manteo.
Where is Ryan Bartell's money?
Maybe the other
three divided it up.
Or there's another two
suitcases hidden somewhere.
Maybe there's some
connection with that
and the drugs found in your car.
That's what I'm saying.
Oh, yeah, they got bail.
I understand you do
a pretty good business
at your garage, Mr. Rose.
I got the best garage in town.
Of course,
you don't really own it, do you?
It's owned by the bank
over in Little Washington,
North Carolina,
or that is, it's
owned by the men
who hold the note that
the bank collects on.
Is that right?
Well, yeah.
Whose names are on the note?
I don't remember.
The names on the
note are Lee Kramer,
David Channing, Ernie D'Amato,
and the late Frank
Hamilton and Ryan Bartell.
Is that right?
I guess so.
And you've missed payments
now and then, haven't you?
Well, m-my divorce caused me...
And they didn't foreclose?
No.
Do you, uh, do you
do things for them?
I-I fix their cars.
Do you lie for them?
Objection.
Sustained.
Didn't my client call you
the evening of the ninth
and ask you to come by
his house the next morning
and fix his car?
I wasn't anywhere near
his house that morning.
Uh, Mr. Rose,
do you own a 1962
Porsche Cabriolet?
Yeah. Restored it myself.
D-Do you drive it or do you
keep it under a roof somewhere?
No, I drive it.
I mean, I, you know, put
a cover on it when I park it,
keep it in the garage at night.
Yeah.
Does anybody else
on the island have
a car like that?
No, sir.
So it was your Porsche Cabriolet
that went through
Roy's Car Wash at 8:30
the morning of the murder.
How do you know that?
Roy Scarborough told me.
He owns the car wash, says
you came in with fresh tree sap
on the hood of your car
and were real anxious
to get it off
before it soaked in
and ruined the paint.
Now, how...
could a car that was
in a garage all night
wind up with tree sap on
it at 8:30 in the morning?
I don't know.
That's a tough one, isn't it?
I think that sap came
from that big tree
outside Spencer
Hamilton's house.
Roy told me that he
was all the time scraping
that same kind of sap
off Frank's car.
You were there the morning
of the murder, weren't you?
All right, I-I-I was there.
And my client was
there, too, wasn't he?
Yeah, he was there.
Who told you to lie?
The, the... man
who hold my note.
There's three of them
left. Which one was it?
I don't, I don't know.
I didn't, uh... I didn't
recognize the voice.
See, one of them, uh, called me,
and he threatened
to take my garage,
and he told me what
to do, and I did it.
No further questions.
Cross-examine.
Mr. Rose, was the
defendant standing right there
while you were fixing his car?
Well, no. He...
Where was he?
He went in the house.
And from where you were working,
could you see to the
back door of the house?
No.
So it's entirely possible
that at one point,
he left the house
through the back door,
met Ryan Bartell in the
woods somewhere, shot him,
and returned to the house
without you seeing him,
isn't it, Mr. Rose?
Yeah.
Sure is possible.
No further questions.
Hey, Gerry, how's it going?
It's going, Conrad. What's up?
You remember that cocaine
bust out of Nags Head last month?
Last month...?
Rudy Clark,
12 ounces. Mind if I have
a look at the evidence?
Anything for Manteo's finest.
Got the inventory?
It's there with the evidence.
Eight?
Well, Commissioner,
even though you say
you're not co-counsel.
The fact is the state of
North Carolina requires
a local co-counsel when
counsel is from another state.
And for Mr. Hamilton,
you're it, right?
Yes, sir, that is correct.
You don't mind being
called as a witness, do you?
Oh, no, no, not at all.
I just don't know how
much help I can be.
Maybe more than you think.
You practice law in
Manteo, don't you?
I have a little practice.
Yeah. In fact, you're
the attorney of record
in a cocaine possession
case against Mr. Rudy Clark,
is that right?
Well...
Yes or no?
Yes.
How much cocaine was seized
at the time of
Mr. Clark's arrest?
Well, it was...
12 ounces, wasn't it?
Uh, yeah, I think
that's about right.
I was recently arrested
and charged for possession
of four ounces of cocaine.
And as it happened,
four ounces of cocaine
turned up missing
from the Sheriff's
Department Property Room.
You know what case
it was missing from?
I have no idea.
The Clark case. Your case.
As counsel of record,
you have access
to that cocaine, don't you?
Just what the hell
are you implying?
I'm not implying anything,
I'm saying right out loud.
You went in that room,
took four ounces of cocaine
out of the Clark evidence,
planted it in my car
in the hopes that my arrest
would end the investigation
into Ryan Bartell's murder.
This is outrageous!
Why would I do a
dumb thing like that?
It was dumb. I'm talking dumb!
Surely you had to know the
Clark case would come up,
and the cocaine
would turn up missing,
and there's not a chance in
hell you're going to get it back.
I didn't take it.
Mr. Lewis, the
cocaine found in my car
and the cocaine stored in
the Sheriff's Property Room
were analyzed. You
know what they found?
No, and I don't appreciate...
The two samples
were exactly the same.
86.2% cocaine.
13.8% mannite.
According to police chemists,
that would be an
extraordinary coincidence
unless both batches
were exactly the same.
What say, Commissioner?
Miss Lyle, isn't there something
you'd like to say at this point?
Yes, objection, Your Honor!
Um, there's no doubt
that his question is
leading to speculation,
and Mr. Matlock is engaging
in rampant speculation himself.
Sustained.
Uh, Mr. Lewis, how well
did you know Ryan Bartell?
I knew who he was.
How well do you know
Lee Kramer, David
Channing Ernie D'Amato?
I know who they are.
Are you aware that they
were recently arrested
in an alleged attempt to
transport huge sums of money
out of the country?
Yes.
Are you aware that an
attempt to catch them doing
the same thing at a different
location earlier in the day
was a dismal failure?
I've heard that.
Your office is next
to the sheriff's office,
and like you say, you
get about a good bit;
like to know what's going on.
I do like to keep up. Yeah.
You drop into the sheriff's
office almost every day.
We're old friends.
According to Deputy
McMasters, you dropped in
at the very moment
that he and the sheriff
were setting up
that first stakeout.
Well, I...
I could have done that, yeah.
Yeah, yeah. Now as you know,
the first stakeout failed.
When Deputy
McMasters, on his own,
set up the second stakeout,
and it was a roaring
success. Why?
I don't know.
It's because as soon as
you heard of the first stakeout,
you left the sheriff's office
and you called Lee
Kramer or Mr. Channing
or one of them and warned them.
No.
You've done little
favors for them for years,
haven't you? Objection.
Speculation.
No, Your Honor. No, Your Honor.
This is not speculation.
The proof is right
outside that door.
Overruled.
For the moment.
Thank you.
Uh, does the number
N-C-9-4-O-2-B-A
mean anything to you?
That's the registration
number on my boat.
Yeah. Silverly. Adamantium.
Sheriff Parks and
Deputy McMasters
found something
interesting in her hold.
Money.
More than a
million-and-a-half in cash.
Was that your reward
for planting the
cocaine in my car?
Or warning them?
Or maybe for
murdering Ryan Bartell?
Murder?
Now, wait a minute.
Just hold on.
I don't know where
that money came from.
Now, I might've done a
few favors for those guys,
like you said; I might've even
done a couple of other things
I shouldn't have done.
But I swear to you, I
never killed anybody.
I was at home that
morning. Ask my wife.
Ask my neighbor. I saw
him out in his backyard
and waved to him. Ask him.
Believe me, after
everything that's happened,
if I knew who murdered
Ryan Bartell, I'd sure tell you.
All I know is, it was not me.
Nothing further.
♪ ♪
You find anything? Not yet.
Hey, look here.
Ryan Bartell kept a new
knife in an old sheath.
That's not the
knife I saw in the bar
the night I broke up the fight
between Ryan and Spencer.
It's not?
Same type of knife,
but this one's brand-new.
Ryan's knife was old,
it was worn down
with sharpening,
and it was nicked.
Are you sure?
I'm positive.
Now, let's see.
You and Lee Kramer
and Ernie D'Amato
were running drugs
and laundering your
profits through here
to offshore banks, weren't you?
On the advice of my attorney,
I invoke my Fifth
Amendment right,
and refuse to answer
on the grounds that it may
intend to incriminate me.
Okay.
Who was Frank Hamilton?
He was a friend you
used to go hunting
and fishing with, wasn't he?
That would be...
That would be you and
Lee Kramer and Ernie
D'Amato and Ryan Bartell.
What happened to Frank Hamilton?
He was shot and killed in a
hunting accident, wasn't he?
Who fired the accidental shot
and killed him?
Who fired the shot?
Ryan Bartell.
Finally.
When did you first
meet Spencer Hamilton,
Frank's brother?
In the Roadhouse Bar.
Day before Ryan was murdered.
Hamilton told Ryan
he didn't believe
that the shooting
was accidental.
Accused him of
murdering his brother. Oh?
What'd Ryan do?
Ryan had a short fuse.
Hamilton called him a liar.
Ryan pulled a knife on him.
What kind of knife?
Hunting knife he always carried.
Aha.
Well, uh, what happened, uh,
after Deputy McMasters
came and broke it up?
Did Spencer leave?
Yeah.
Yeah. Stabbed
the knife in the table
and left.
Did you get the feeling
that he was gonna
stay around town
and start, uh, digging?
Surely you and your
friends must've known
that sooner or later,
we would stumble onto
your drug operation.
So you and your coconspirators
decided to kill Ryan Bartell
and frame Spencer Hamilton.
Killing two birds
with one stone,
so to speak. On the advice
of my attorney, I invoke my...
Now either you elected
on your own
or were chosen... to kill him.
But your reward was Ryan
Bartell's money, wasn't it?
On the advice of my attorney...
And then you got deeper
and deeper in trouble.
You planted that money
on Gordon Lewis's boat
to make him
look like the killer.
On the advice of my attorney...
All right, all right.
Do you recognize this knife?
That's Ryan's hunting knife.
Well, it is and it isn't.
It was found in
Mr. Bartell's home
and in the sheath that
Mr. Bartell always wore,
but Mr. Bartell
carried the same knife
five years or more.
It was all scratched and nicked.
This is brand-new, isn't it?
I don't know. Huh.
This knife was bought
on June the 10th at Hudson
Sporting Goods Store.
The clerk said the
man she sold it to,
showed her an old knife
and said he wanted
another one just like it.
That person was you, wasn't it?
No.
But why change knives?
There must've been
something on that old knife
that implicated you.
Maybe there was
some of your blood on it.
And that's why you
exchanged them, wasn't it?
I don't know what
you're talking about.
So, you say, "Why not
"just wash the blood
off the old knife?
Why get a new knife?"
And a few years ago,
that might've worked.
But anymore, police
science is so exact,
say you got a knife,
got blood on it...
You wash it off, can't be
seen with the naked eye...
The police with their
equipment can still find
what is called trace evidence.
Still traces of blood.
And they can be so exact,
they can tell you the type,
how long it's been there
and probably whose.
And you knew it
was yours, didn't you?
After you shot Ryan Bartell,
he stabbed you, didn't he?
Your Honor, I must object.
Pure speculation.
No, Your Honor, this
is not speculation at all.
We'll see,
Mr. Matlock. Overruled.
Let me try to be more
exact, Mr. Channing.
You shot him.
The first shot didn't kill him.
He rose up and plunged
his knife into your leg.
Your second shot did him in.
Uh...
You were real busy
the morning Ryan
Bartell was killed.
You shot him, he stabbed
you, you shot him again.
You took the
sheath off his body.
Picked up the knife, planted
the gun at Spencer's house.
Then you had to do something
about the blood on your leg.
Handkerchief or something.
Then you went to
Greenville, bought a new knife,
got rid of the old knife,
then you could
go to the hospital
and have something done
about the two-inch
gash in your leg.
How am I doing?
No.
That was your blood
on that old knife.
We called all the
hospitals in the vicinity,
and there's several people
at the hospital up in Greenville
who remember you.
Said you came in
with a bloody thigh.
It wasn't me.
There are two people
in the gallery right now
ready to identify you.
Well, they're wrong.
There's a simple
way we can settle this.
The scar, if there is
one, would be about here.
We can go in judge's
chambers, take a look,
or I've got a pocket knife.
We can split your
pants... up about that far.
There's no scar,
you're home free.
We'll get you a
new pair of pants.
What say?
I have got a little scar
from when I was working
on a propeller of my boat.
Nothing further.
We find the defendant,
Spencer Hamilton,
not guilty.
Thank you, ladies and gentlemen.
This court is adjourned.
Okay, see, now,
this is important.
Don't touch this;
this is the flash.
Just look through this
little square box here
and then push that... I
know how to take a picture!
Thank you. What a
nice-looking group here.
Thanks, thanks.
Well, Mr. Matlock,
thanks for everything.
And good luck, good luck to you.
Thanks, Conrad. Yeah, thank you.
Me first!
Della Basnight.
Uh, Conrad, I'm glad to have
met you and worked with you.
And so am I glad to
have met you, Mr. Matlock.
This is Jimmy;
Jimmy is a Basnight.
It's good, huh? Yeah.
Especially winning. Aw.
Bobby... Winning tastes
good, doesn't it? Yes.
Bobby's an Owen, but
he married a Basnight.
Look, uh, next time you
come, we'll keep it a secret.
I'll take you blue fishing. Oh!
This is Betty Alice Mann.
Bluefish, listen, if you
come to Atlanta, I know...
This is John
Wilton; he's a cousin.
But hell, everybody
on the island's a cousin!
You come to Atlanta, I know
a place where there's catfish.
You can't catch any, but
you can buy all you want!
This is Mama!
Smile.
Aah...
♪ When it's peach
picking time in Georgia ♪
♪ Apple picking
time in Tennessee ♪
♪ Cotton picking
time in Mississippi ♪
♪ Everybody picks on me. ♪
Playing our song.
Well, Conrad!
Get in here!
What you doing in Atlanta?!
Oh, I had a little vacation.
How much vacation? A lot.
I never really took one.
You never... sit down!
You know, in Manteo, it's
hard to tell vacation from work.
Neither one's exactly
strenuous. Oh, yeah.
How is Manteo?
Oh, Manteo...
Manteo's great. Yeah?
Everybody misses you,
wishes you'd come back.
Oh, I will, I will.
So, what are your
plans during vacation?
Well, I-I... I have
no real plans.
I thought I'd just
stop and see you.
So...
So, I have, so I
guess I'll be going.
What?
Well, wait.
Wait a minute.
Ar-Are you saying
you've got some
free time while
you're on vacation?
Yeah, a little.
Why? Oh.
Well, see, I've got this client,
and he's up for murder
one, but he didn't do it.
I'm pretty sure
it was a mob hit.
But now I've got to prove it.
Mob, huh? Yeah. It's dangerous.
I mean...
there's some...
very bad dudes.
Gonna take a lot
of investigating.
A lot of investigating?
A lot, yeah.
You know, if you
need some help...
Oh, no, no, no, no, no.
I wouldn't want to
interfere with your holiday...
You wouldn't, no, you wouldn't.
No, I-I-I really want to help.
Well...
And it shows, doesn't it?
Yeah, it does, Conrad.
It's, it's, it's all
over you. Yeah.
You like a little
excitement, huh?
Yeah, well, you need some help.
Looks like we were
meant for each other.
I hope so.
B and C. No.
C and B. C and B.
www.tvsubtitles.net